

CONTACT

- tinatanasova@hotmail.com
- **** 015750738432
- Von-Eichendorff-Straße 6
 Markt Schwaben

EXPERTISE

- Sales and Retail
- Social Media Marketing
- Innovative Graphic Solutions
- Content Management

SOFTWARE

- Microsoft Office Apps (Word, Excel, PowerPoint & Publisher)
- Google Apps (Docs, Sheets & Drive)
- WEB Building Apps (WIX, Shopify & WordPress)
- Design & Editing Apps (Autodesk Sketchbook, Infinite Painter, Ibis Painter & Canva)

LANGUAGES

- Macedonian (Native)
- English (IELTS Level C1)
- Serbian/Croatian (Level C1)

TINA ATANASOVA

Creative and motivated professional with exceptional skills in planning, analytical thinking and executing strategies. A proven expert in successfully managing ad projects from concept to completion in the leisure, business travel and tourism industry. Adaptive personality with an ability to work with a team or independently, creating effectiveness and developing opportunities that further deliver the desired results.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SHIPPING COORDINATOR

11.2021 - 10.2022

Mytheresa

- Packaged luxury items in exclusive gift boxes
- Quality control of luxury items

TRAVEL SPECIALIST

09.2018 - 03.2021

Golden Tour

- Managed hotel and air ticket reservations
- Direct and indirect sales and invoicing
- Created designs and new concepts for product promotions
- Managed marketing campaigns (newsletters, posts, ads)
- Built and updated company's website

TRAVEL CONSULTANT

11.2009 - 08.2018

BTI Macedonia

- Managed hotel and rail reservations
- Organized meetings, incentives, conferences and events
- Direct and indirect sales and invoicing
- Did graphics for promotional materials

EDUCATION

SEE UNIVERSITY Tetovo

2004 - 2009

Bachelor's Degree in English Language and Literature

CERTIFICATES

- Galileo Selling Platform
- Amadeus Selling Platform
- IATA (International Air Transport Association)

SIDE PROJECTS

- www.ncpropertyinspections.com
- www.goldentour.com.mk